Let's quickly have a look at the system requirements to set up a new be build in your.
Hardware requirements.
A 64 bit system is required to build as a side note in case if you don't have a 64 bit mission, you
can also build an older Android version before Gingerbread in a 32 bit mission.
You need at least 250 GB to check out the code.
Add another extra 150 GB to build it.
So overall, you need 400 GB of this base to download and build areas.
So before downloading and building AOSP, make sure you have 400 GB displays.
I would also recommend using an SSD hard disk since it could significantly increase your disk IO performance,
and that has a huge impact on the overall performance.
Also, please note that if you want to build multiple flavors of Android, you would need more space
for each build.
So, for example, you are building multiple variants of mobile platform.
So in that case, you would need another extra 150 GB for each build the gradient.
So at least 16GB of RAM is required.
And Google recommends 64 GB, but I guess 16 or 32GB also should be just fine.
That's from my personal experience.
I'm using a system with 16 Core and 32 GB RAM.
It takes approximately around one hour, 20 minutes to complete the entire build.
Google is saying that are using 72 core missions with 64 GB of RAM, which takes about 40 minutes for
a complete bill that seriously a end mission.
But of course, you can build areas, be in a labyrinth system.
The only drawback is that you have more waiting hours for the bill to complete.
Another option which you could consider in case if you don't have about permission is to have a high
end mission in the cloud and do the big, then that's pretty cheap.
Check out this link window on an oblivious.
So here you have lot of cheaper options where you can get a 64 commissions say for one hour and use
it for the purpose and then shut it down.
So the lingo these you are is attached in the description.
So no software requirements.
I spoke to Google, the only oil supporter.
As of now, he's open.
So in the past before Android to Mac OS was supported.
But I guess since Apple switched to ARM architecture, it's no more officially supported.
I have once built AOSP 11 in Mac M1 with half success.
I heard that's the video link here in case if you are interested, please having.